Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. POLITICAL ACTIVITIES 1973-98
  - Campaigns
    - Governor's race, 1998
      - Media activities
        - Press releases and statements (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Ads (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - 1998 Congressional election (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Reference materials
      - Emily's List (Box 33)
        - Guide to Campaign Fundraising for Democratic Women Candidates, "Making the Dough Rise" 1995 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - Guide to Campaign Fundraising for Democratic Women Candidates, "Making the Dough Rise" (1995) (cont'd) (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Press Secretary Training Manual 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee (DCCC)
        - Manual on Campaign Research (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Incumbent training seminar notebook, Jun 1994 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
        - 1996 DCCC Campaign Planning and Management Workbook (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
        - Special election information book, Oct 1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Democratic National Committee campaign publications (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
- SERIES IV. LEGISLATIVE FILES 1993-98
  - Voting and attendance records, 103rd-104th Congresses, 1993-96 (Box 34)
    - 103rd-104th Congresses, 1993-96 (Box 35, Folder 1-8)
    - 105th Congress, 1997-98 (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
  - Bills sponsored/cosponsored, 103rd-105th Congresses, 1993-98
    - 103rd-105th Congresses (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
    - Legislative profiles, 104th-105th Congresses (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
  - Co-signed letters, 105th Congress, 1997-98
    - Part 1 (Box 36, Folder 10-15)
    - Part 2 (Box 37, Folder 1-83)
    - Part 3 (Box 38, Folder 1-15)
  - House National Security Committee
    [Closed untilJanuary 1, 2029]
    - 104th Congress, 1995-96 (Box 38)
      - B-2 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Bid protest/acquisition reform (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Defense (Box 38)
        - Healthcare (Box 38, Folder 18-20)
        - Spending priorities (Box 38, Folder 21)
        - Women's issues (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
      - Dept. of Defense
        - Authorization - Personnel FY 97 (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Ban on gay service personnel (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Retirees-36th Congressional District (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Export loan guarantee (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Federally Funded Research and Development Centers (FFRDC) (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Former Dept. of Defense spouse, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Heavy bomber industrial capabilities study (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - HIV discharge repeal, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 40, Folder 3-5)
      - HR 1350 - Maritime Security Act (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - HR 1530 - Dept. of Defense Conference Report (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - HR 1530 - FY 96 Defense Authorization (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - HR 3230 markup - FY 97 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Maritime Administration (MARAD) (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - MARAD FY 97 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Maritime Advisory Committee (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Maritime Panel: general, markup (Box 41, Folder 5-7)
      - Military personnel - FY 97 (Box 41, Folder 8-9)
      - Minuteman III (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - MRE/donated foods amendment (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - National Defense Authorization - FY 97 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Oversight Panel on the Merchant Marine, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Personnel Subcommittee mark-up FY 96 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - POW-MIA issues (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Retired pay compensation (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Shipbuilding - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development agreement, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Technology Reinvestment Program (TRP) - dual use (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Western Regional Law Enforcement and Technology Center (Box 42)
        - Part 1 (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Part 2 (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
      - Youth Challenge program (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - 105th Congress, 1997-98
      - Aerospace Advisory Committee (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - B-2 bomber (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Big Think - future defense requirements (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - COSCO (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
      - COSCO/Port of Long Beach (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Defense (Box 44)
        - Authorization markup FY 98 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Environmental issues (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - Export loan guarantee program (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Reductions (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Defense Authorization Conference FY 98 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Dual use - FY 98 Dept. of Defense (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - F/A-18 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Federally Funded Research and Development Centers (FFRDC) (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Gays in the military (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
      - HIV-positive nonworldwide-deployable service personnel (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - MARAD - FY 98 Authorization (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Maritime Advisory Committee: general, visit to DC (Box 45, Folder 3-5)
      - McVeigh, CPO Timothy (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - National Defense Authorization Act
        - FY98 - FY99, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
        - FY99 - Personnel issues (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Oversight Panel on the Merchant Marine (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Personnel markup - FY 98 Dept. of Defense Authorization (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - POW-MIA issues (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Procurement reform, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - RAND defense consolidation study (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Scorpius (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Legislative staff files
    - Legislative assignments, 1996-98 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Maria Alongi (Box 46)
      - Appropriations FY 1999 (Box 46)
        - Agriculture (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - Commerce-State-Justice (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - Democratic initiatives - Omnibus (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - District of Columbia (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - Foreign operations (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - Interior (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - Labor-Health and Human Services-Education (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
        - Omnibus (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - Transportation (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Treasury-Postal (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Veterans Administration-Housing and Urban Development (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - California issues/research
        - Business (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - Child care (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - Education (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
        - Health care (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - Immigration (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - Important articles (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - Welfare (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Foreign policy-105th
        - American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) (Box 49, Folder 2-3)
        - American Jewish Congress - Sep 1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - Bosnia (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - China bills, Nov 1997 (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - Cyprus Enclaved Resolution (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - Dayton Peace Accords (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - Foreign Policy Reform Act (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - Greek issues (Box 49, Folder 10)
        - Industrial College of the Armed Forces (ICAF) presentation (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - Intel Authorization FY 98 - Whistle-blower protection (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - Israel, 50th Anniversary (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - Middle East peace process (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - Mordechai visit (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - Non-proliferation (Box 50, Folder 6-7)
        - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) (Box 50)
          - Enlargement (Box 50, Folder 8-9)
          - Op-ed (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - North Korea (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - North Korea launch (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Perry Conference (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - U.S.-Iran relations, "Crossfire," Jan 1998 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - U.S.-Israeli Interparliamentary Commission - missiles (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Immigration-104th & 105th
        - Immigration reform (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
        - Reimbursement to California for education of illegal immigrants (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Supplemental Security Income (SSI) benefits for immigrants (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Legislative initiatives-105th
        - Choice Amendment - FY 1999 (Box 51)
          - Part 1 (Box 51, Folder 11-12)
          - Part 2 (Box 52, Folder 1-5)
        - Encryption (Box 52, Folder 6-15)
          [Closed until January 1, 2029]
        - HR 411 - Abortion at military facilities (Box 53, Folder 1-9)
        - Russia-Iran (Box 53)
          - Part 1 (Box 53, Folder 10-28)
          - Part 2 (Box 54, Folder 1-12)
        - Vaccines for Children (VFC) program (Box 54)
          - Part 1 (Box 54, Folder 13-16)
          - Part 2 (Box 55, Folder 1-14)
    - Bryan Banks
      - Agriculture, 1998 (Box 55)
        - Appropriations (Box 55, Folder 15)
        - Bass/DeFazio appropriations amendment (Box 55, Folder 16)
        - California citrus (Box 55, Folder 17)
        - California vs. El Niño (Box 55, Folder 18)
        - Farm crisis (Box 55, Folder 19)
        - General issues (Box 55, Folder 20)
        - H-2 visa program - "Bracero" (Box 55, Folder 21)
        - Miller/Schumer sugar appropriations amendment (Box 55, Folder 22)
        - Most Favored Nation & Fast Track Trade Authority (Box 55, Folder 23)
        - Neuman/Kanjorski peanut appropriations amendment (Box 55, Folder 24)
        - Northeast Dairy Compact (Box 55, Folder 25)
        - Point Reyes California Farmland Preservation Act (Box 55, Folder 26)
        - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture rural development - Val Dolcini (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Arts issues, 1998
        - Congressional art competition (Box 55, Folder 28)
        - General (Box 55, Folder 29)
        - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Immigration, 1998
        - H1-B visa increase (Box 56, Folder 1-4)
        - Haitian refugee relief (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - Illegal immigration (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - Naturalization (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Native Americans, 1998
        - Gaming (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Sovereignty (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Veterans (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Transportation, 1998
        - Airline industry (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - Alameda Corridor (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Appropriations "Dear Colleague" letters (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - Metropolitan Transportation Authority (Box 57, Folder 7-9)
      - Miscellaneous issues, 1998
        - High Tech (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Postal operations (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - U.S. Treasury (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - David Flanders
      - Notes, undated (Box 57)
        - Part 1 (Box 58, Folder 1-21)
        - Part 2 (Box 59, Folder 1-15)
      - FY 1996 budget and appropriations
        - Agriculture (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - Appropriations information (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - Budget (Box 59)
          - Part 1 (Box 59, Folder 18-19)
          - Part 2 (Box 60, Folder 1-6)
        - Commerce-State-Justice (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - Defense (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - District of Columbia (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - Emergency Rescissions and Supplemental (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - Energy and Water (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Foreign Operations (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - Interior (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - Labor-Health and Human Services-Education (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - Legislative Branch (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - Military Construction (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - Omnibus (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - Transportation (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - Treasury-Postal (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - Veterans Administration-Housing and Urban Development (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - FY 1997 budget and appropriations
        - Agriculture (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - Budget (Box 62, Folder 7-9)
        - Commerce-State-Justice (Box 62, Folder 10)
        - District of Columbia (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - Emergency Supplemental (Box 62, Folder 12)
        - Energy and Water (Box 62, Folder 13)
        - Labor-Health and Human Services-Education (Box 62, Folder 14)
        - Legislative Branch (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Military Construction (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Omnibus (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Transportation (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Treasury-Postal (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Veterans Administration-Housing and Urban Development (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - FY 1998 appropriations bills
        - Agriculture (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Budget reconciliation (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Commerce-State-Justice (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - Defense (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - District of Columbia (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - Energy and Water (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Foreign Operations (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Interior (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - Labor-Health and Human Services-Education (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Legislative Branch (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Military Construction (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Transportation (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Treasury-Postal (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - Veterans Administration-Housing and Urban Development (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Danny Geffen
      - Crime, 1995-97 (Box 65)
        - Asset forfeiture (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - Assault weapons (Box 65, Folder 8)
        - Child pornography (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Child protection (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Community Oriented Policing Services (COPS) program (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - Crime - general (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Domestic violence gun ban (Box 66, Folder 5)
        - Drugs (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - Federal Bureau of Investigations due process for agents (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Feinstein gangs bill (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - Flag burning (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - Guns - Brady bill (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - Jail (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Juvenile justice (Box 66, Folder 12)
        - Law and Technology Centers (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Lazarovich, Shayna (Box 66, Folder 14)
        - Legal Services Corporation (Box 66, Folder 15)
        - Mexico - drugs (Box 66, Folder 16)
        - Police benefits (Box 66, Folder 17)
        - Waco (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Foreign affairs, 105th Congress, 1997-98
        - Bosnia (Box 66, Folder 19)
        - Croatia (Box 66, Folder 20)
        - Foreign arms sales (Box 66, Folder 21)
        - Foreign Operations appropriations FY 97 (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - HR 2652 - School of the Americas (Box 66, Folder 23)
        - Human rights (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - Israel - foreign aid (Box 67, Folder 2)
        - Israel/Palestine Liberation Organization vs. terrorism (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - Jerusalem (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - Jewish issues (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - Middle East peace process (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
        - Nuclear arms (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC) (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
        - "Peace through Strength" National Security Caucus (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Qaddafy/Farrakhan (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - State Department Authorization FY 98 (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Syria (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - U.S. arms sales (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Foreign affairs, miscellaneous, 103rd-105th, 1993-98
        - Africa (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - Albania (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - Asia - general (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Brazil (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - Burma/Myanmar (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - Cuba (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - East Timor/Indonesia (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - El Salvador (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Foreign aid (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Foreign aid authorization, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Greece and Macedonia (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Guatemala (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Haiti (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - India/Pakistan/Kashmir (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Iran (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Iraq (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Japan (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Macedonia (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Mexico (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Newly Independent States (NIS) (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Persian Gulf (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - Puerto Rico (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Russia (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Russia/Commonwealth of Independent States (Box 70, Folder 3-4)
        - Taiwan (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Vietnam (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Immigration, 1995-97
        - Administrative (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - Attacks on immigration groups (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Benefits (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - Birthright citizenship (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - Border control (Box 70, Folder 11-12)
        - Californians for Population Stabilization (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Cost data/studies (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Deportation, visa overstays (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - General (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - HR 2202 - Immigration in the National Interest Act of 1995 (Box 71)
          - Part 1 (Box 71, Folder 5-21)
          - Part 2 (Box 72, Folder 1-18)
        - Immigration technology (Box 72, Folder 19)
        - Legal, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 72, Folder 20)
        - Naturalization (Box 72, Folder 21)
        - Reimbursement to states (Box 72, Folder 22)
        - Taskforce on Immigration Reform (Box 72, Folder 23)
        - Temerula incident, Apr 1996 (Box 72, Folder 24)
        - Workplace enforcement (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Trade, 1995-97
        - Bananas (Box 73, Folder 1)
        - Border Trade Alliance (Box 73, Folder 2)
        - Burma sanctions - con (Box 73, Folder 3)
        - Fast track (Box 73, Folder 4)
        - Financial sources (Box 73, Folder 5)
        - Information technology access (Box 73, Folder 6)
        - Israel (Box 73, Folder 7)
        - Japan - U.S. (Box 73, Folder 8)
        - Japan (from Japan) (Box 73, Folder 9)
        - Japan (from U.S.) (Box 73, Folder 10)
        - Japan (press) (Box 73, Folder 11)
        - Labor/Industry Coalition for International Trade (Box 73, Folder 12)
        - Lumber (Box 73, Folder 13)
        - Mexico bailout (Box 74, Folder 1)
        - Middle East (Box 74, Folder 2)
        - Romania MFN (Box 74, Folder 3)
        - Semiconductors (China/Japan) (Box 74, Folder 4)
        - Short supply (Box 74, Folder 5)
        - U.N. peacekeeping (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1995-96
        - Armenian National Committee of America (Box 74, Folder 7)
        - Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) gun studies funding (Box 74, Folder 8)
        - Church arson (Box 74, Folder 9)
        - Franking file, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 10)
        - Gay issues (Box 74, Folder 11)
        - Information superhighway (Box 74, Folder 12)
        - Internet use in Harman offices (Box 74, Folder 13)
        - Job training info (Box 74, Folder 14)
        - Legal Services Corporation (Box 74, Folder 15)
        - "Modem Tax" (Box 74, Folder 16)
        - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 74, Folder 17)
        - "Press Freedom Abuses in Turkey - April 1996 Update" (Box 74, Folder 18)
        - Public Broadcasting (Box 74, Folder 19)
        - Terrorism bill (Box 74, Folder 20-21)
        - Terrorism bill (cont'd) (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
        - Thank yous (Box 75, Folder 3)
        - U.S. Sentencing Commission - Annual Report 1995 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Danny Geffen and Maria Alongi
      - Choice, 1993-98 (Box 75)
        - Abortions at military facilities, 103rd & 104th (Box 75, Folder 5)
        - Anti-choice bills, 105th Congress, 1st session (Box 75, Folder 6)
        - Appropriations FY 97 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Background information, 1997-98 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - California Title X clinics (Box 75, Folder 9)
        - Child Custody Protection Act (Box 75, Folder 10)
        - Clinic violence (Box 75, Folder 11)
        - HR 1946 - Parental Rights (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - Insurance coverage (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - International family planning (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - Istook amendment, 104th Congress (Box 76, Folder 4)
        - NARAL Congressional Tally on Choice (Box 76, Folder 5)
        - Parental notification (Box 76, Folder 6)
        - "Partial birth" abortion (Box 76, Folder 7)
        - "Partial birth" veto override (Box 76, Folder 8)
        - RU486 (Box 76, Folder 9)
        - Speeches on choice-103rd (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Education - 104th-105th, 1995-98
        - Census (Box 76, Folder 11)
        - Class size reduction, FY 99 (Box 76, Folder 12)
        - Cuts in 104th Congress (Box 76, Folder 13-14)
        - Educational equity (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - El Camino/Title III (Box 77, Folder 2)
        - Enrollment increases (Box 77, Folder 3)
        - General (Box 77, Folder 4-6)
        - Goals 2000 (Box 77, Folder 7)
        - Harman record, education (Box 77, Folder 8)
        - Head Start (Box 77, Folder 9)
        - Higher Education Reauthorization (Box 77, Folder 10)
        - HR 123 - English Only (Box 77, Folder 11)
        - HR 3892 - English fluency (Box 77, Folder 12)
        - Individuals with Disabilities Education Act (IDEA) (Box 78, Folder 1)
        - Job training (Box 78, Folder 2)
        - Presidential scholarships (Box 78, Folder 3)
        - Primary and secondary funds (Box 78, Folder 4)
        - School lunch (Box 78, Folder 5)
        - Technology (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Letters, 1994-98
        - AIDS Healthcare Foundation (Box 78, Folder 7)
        - Argentina trade barriers - Mattel (Box 78, Folder 8)
        - Assistive technology (Box 78, Folder 9)
        - Berenson, Lori (Box 78, Folder 10)
        - Bowers ambulance services (Box 78, Folder 11)
        - Breast cancer - Dept. of Defense appropriations FY 96 (Box 78, Folder 12)
        - Breast cancer research funding (Box 78, Folder 13)
        - California State University (CSU) bond cap (Box 78, Folder 14)
        - Community Nursing Organization (CNO) project (Box 78, Folder 15)
        - Dept. of Energy National Security programs (Box 78, Folder 16)
        - Disproportionate Share Hospitals (DSH) (Box 78, Folder 17)
        - E-Rate (Box 78, Folder 18)
        - Electricity deregulation (Box 78, Folder 19)
        - H-1 B (Box 78, Folder 20)
        - Harbor-UCLA Medical Foundation, Inc. (MFI) (Box 78, Folder 21)
        - Health care reform - abortion coverage (Box 78, Folder 22)
        - HIV/AIDS prevention (Box 78, Folder 23)
        - HONDA-Ultra Low Emission Vehicle (ULEV) (Box 78, Folder 24)
        - Immigration and Naturalization Service inspectors (Box 78, Folder 25)
        - India (Box 78, Folder 26)
        - International Monetary Fund funding (Box 78, Folder 27)
        - Istook amendment - Labor/HHS FY 96 (Box 78, Folder 28)
        - Job Corps (Box 78, Folder 29)
        - Medicaid abortion - Clinton (Box 78, Folder 30)
        - Medicaid for mentally disabled (Box 78, Folder 31)
        - Medicare reimbursement for mammography (Box 78, Folder 32)
        - Medicare - letter to seniors (Box 78, Folder 33)
        - Mexico prisoner transfer (Box 78, Folder 34)
        - Middle East peace process (Box 78, Folder 35)
        - Molina Medical Center (Box 78, Folder 36)
        - Natural gas - Dept. of Energy (Box 78, Folder 37)
        - Nursing education (Box 78, Folder 38)
        - P.E.A.C.H., Inc. - Qualified Medicare Beneficiaries (QMB) (Box 78, Folder 39)
        - Sanchez-Dornan (Box 79, Folder 1)
        - School libraries (Box 79, Folder 2)
        - Sexually transmitted disease (STD) research and prevention (Box 79, Folder 3)
        - Social Security reform (Box 79, Folder 4)
        - State Justice Institute - Programs for Women (Box 79, Folder 5)
        - Suffrage statues (Box 79, Folder 6)
        - Teen pregnancies (Box 79, Folder 7)
        - Terrorist attack in Jerusalem (Box 79, Folder 8)
        - Tobacco letter to Gingrich (Box 79, Folder 9)